NETFLIX PRESENTS
["Queen of the Night" aria
from Mozart's The Magic Flute playing]
[no audible sound effects]
[aria continues]
[audible crash]
[aria ends]
[stuttering] Maybe I went a bit nuts.
[man] How do you think
your daughter feels, seeing you like that?
[sighs softly]
Well, Diego, perhaps
you should reflect on the
fact that certain decisions were made
because your behavior might have an impact
on your daughter's frame of mind.
Since your divorce, you've been
in and out of places like this.
But the guy wouldn't just put
the flour back,
and… and I kept on telling him…
I was working.
You know? He kept moving the flour on me.
It's like, uh,
you put your cell phone right here
and I moved it there,
so you put it back here.
I moved it over there,
and you want to put it
right back where you want it
because that's your phone's place.
But I move it back there,
and hey, maybe…
m-maybe that would wind you up too, no?
[inhales deeply] You seem to be telling me
that your behavior,
losing your job, all of it,
was because this person happened
to move your flour around too much?
You know how much power you give up
when you react like this?
Hmm.
M-Maybe I was already
just a bit on edge.
It's just, my ex-wife always
treats me like I'm an idiot.
She seems to think that
I'm not a good father.
And she… she mustn't think
that I'm not a good father.
However,
we don't have much control
over the things your ex-wife thinks.
It would be much more useful
to work towards you, Diego,
not thinking these things about yourself.
[upbeat music playing softly]
[breathing deeply, sniffing]
[camera beeps]
[clears throat]
Are you watching carefully?
None of this here…
Yes, none of this
would've been possible before right now.
Right now, though…
Right now,
it is.
[chuckles softly]
Yes, good afternoon.
I was telling you that last night
I was at this party at the pool.
And somebody decided to push me in
with everything on, my clothes, my shoes.
Although my cell phone?
Intact.
It works perfectly.
[laughs]
The new Z6.
Amazing is nothing!
[chuckles]
[man 1] Come on, let's get serious here.
Do you know what "serious" means?
When you say something,
you have to do it--
[man 2] The delivery man didn't show up.
How does the bread--
[man 1] The bread was supposed
to be ready. You didn't have it ready.
[man 2] He wouldn't have gotten there
if the delivery man wasn't there--
The bread wasn't ready. It must be said.
-Fuck you!
-[man 1] He doesn't get it.
We decide
whether or not to do something, eh?
You think the decision is mine?
We're the doubles.
-Goddamn it!
-[woman] Fuck you harder!
Susanna, calm down. Calm, calm.
Okay, Armando. We're listening.
You can go to Papua New Guinea
if you think I'm a liar.
There, they have freedom.
We're only doubling for them here.
Our real selves are there.
Here, we're only doubles.
Everyone is really there, but that's okay.
The important thing is to admit it.
[man 3] So, you, Armando,
are telling us that you don't feel free.
But here, we aren't forcing you
to do anything.
Of course not, because it's
much more treacherous as a captive.
I don't decide
whether or not to make bread.
Uh, you're a double too.
Who do you think decides whether or not
you get to be the psychiatrist?
-I mean, it's clear--
-Clara, it'd be nice if you were on time.
[Susanna] Fuck you!
Yeah, but I had
a doctor's appointment for the old lady.
-No, but I have more to say.
-Wait a moment, Armando. Sorry.
It wasn't your shift today, Clara,
was it, though?
I didn't think so, but they're always
asking you to do stuff at the last minute,
as if you have nothing else to do.
Next time, could you refrain
from eating during our group?
-Groceries. Hmm…
-[Armando] No.
I, um… skipped lunch,
so I wouldn't be late.
-No, I have more to say. I wasn't done.
-[Susanna] Fuck you! Fuck you!
Paris, why are you looking at me
like that? Tomorrow, I'm done here, so…
I'm going back to my life.
Um, also, my new play is opening soon.
Uh, I'm pretty excited.
So, who's the new guy?
You got caught jacking off in the park?
[man 1 laughing]
-[soft piano music playing]
-[lock clicking repeatedly]
[TV chattering faintly]
[man] How did it go at the day care today?
Fine, fine.
[man] Do they give you any time
to go look for a job,
or do they expect you
to stay there all day?
Sure, but slowly.
I'm gonna get a job. Let me fit in first.
Yes, fit in.
Diego…
Do you know anything about penguins?
Penguins have the unique ability
to excrete their feces
with a force that is
ten times the power of a human being.
A rifle shot!
They don't do it on purpose.
Huh? Nature has everything taken care of.
In order to keep the nest clean,
they spray it away, like explosive!
Imagine, a little seal happens to pass by
and finds himself full of shit.
And, of course, the seal gets angry.
And this pissed-off seal,
this pissed-off seal is wrong here
because the penguin is made that way.
The penguin is never going to change.
The penguin is me.
It's me. I am the penguin.
-And I have no intention of changing--
-And do you… do you think I'm having fun?
Listen, two grown men,
unless they're a couple,
it's impossible for them to live together.
They're like two convicts. Okay?
Now, tomorrow, you go out and find a job,
and make a commitment
to stop freaking out at work.
Those guys, they were total dickheads
b-because the only thing…
they wanted was to have me fired.
Yes, of course, of course.
The dickhead is always somebody else.
The fact is,
the real dickhead is sitting right here.
Because you have a daughter,
and then you go crazy, you lose your job,
and it all falls apart.
[bangs table]
[woman] Afternoon.
Ciao, sweetheart.
-You have 30 minutes, all right?
-[Diego] Yes, yes, I know.
Ciao.
Sit… sit here.
How are you?
Good?
Uh, I… I've got something.
Two juices.
Apricot because it's… it's your favorite.
And look, it's organic,
so, your mom should be happy.
[Diego sniffs]
Hmm…
Uh…
And how is school going?
Good.
Brava.
Hmm…
[Diego sucks straw]
Papa, you…
you've lost weight.
Only a little bit.
But I'm…
I'm solid, I'm fine.
Well… well, don't worry, I'm putting
everything back together.
Everything.
[judge] The Court of Rome,
after re-examining the case
of Mrs. Clara Pagani,
confirms a further six months
of attendance
at the day care center
to which she was previously assigned.
-Talk to her, right?
-No.
-Say something!
-Sh!
-This is because of that asshole Paris.
[judge] Since this sentence is
an alternative to imprisonment,
your attendance, ma'am, is mandatory,
under penalty of imprisonment.
Okay?
This case is scheduled
for review again on May sixth.
But I didn't do anything!
-[lawyer] Sh!
-No, I didn't do anything.
No. No, no, no.
Your Honor, please let me explain
about the original sentencing.
-You must not have--
-You and I shouldn't have direct contact.
-It was an accident.
-Please move.
This is my life!
Is there someone I can talk to?
Please, ma'am, listen to me.
Was everybody in agreement on this?
Hey!
[Clara screams]
[melancholic music playing]
Hey! Hey, Paris!
What, are you fucking with me, huh?
Next time you write me a shitty report,
maybe mention it to me first?
I'm an actress.
I've got a show starting next week
and there's a tour I need to prepare for.
Who's going to talk to my manager?
Because you're driving me crazy!
-Stay calm.
-I'm going crazy!
You're in here because you've done things
that have consequences.
It was an accident.
I never meant to set him on fire.
It was just…
-It was bad luck.
-You refuse to cooperate.
-And won't follow a program.
-Another six months in this fucking place!
-I'm normal!
-You won't recognize the problem.
-Normal!
-Listen! Listen!
I would say you're pretty fortunate
that I delivered my report
before this so-called "normalcy" suggested
you attack a judge in the parking lot!
But when I attacked the judge, and even
right now, there was nobody to talk to.
-You can't even talk.
-Clara, where the fuck are you going?
[distant chatter]
Okay, you have a problem.
All right?
It's not a coincidence.
You're not here for fun.
You need to get that through your head.
[soft piano music playing]
-[woman groans]
-Push. Now push.
Sorry. It hurts.
-Whoa!
-What?
-She says it hurts.
-Did you bring the X-ray?
No.
[woman] Your cousin Giacomo
must have stolen it from me.
I'll ask him,
so he can be sure to bring it next time.
-[man] Good.
-I'll make a note.
[man] Good.
Anna is
the only good granddaughter I have.
All the rest, forget about it.
[chuckles]
[man] Stop.
[woman groans]
-[man] That's okay.
-[woman groans]
[Clara] Hey!
Slowly.
Slow down.
[Susanna] Fuck you, fuck you!
Sorry.
I understand them,
because he was just five.
Stick it up your ass!
He was five years old, my grandson,
and the thing is, well,
I never see him.
Fucking stick it up your ass!
I miss him.
It makes me so sad I can't see him.
And besides the pain,
do any other feelings come up
when you think about this?
I feel shame.
A lot.
Susanna, if you focus on the fact
that this is just your pathology,
and it isn't anything you do on purpose,
does that help you feel better?
How does she do that?
They treat her like she's leprosy.
[man] Oh!
How long since you saw him last?
[Susanna sniffs]
Months?
Years!
You seem angry about this, Clara.
Of course. It's been years!
You see someone like this,
instead of helping her, they're afraid?
No, no. They might not be afraid.
It could be because they wanted
to keep the child
from something hard to understand.
Susanna, you're right
to tell everyone to fuck off.
[Diego chuckles]
[woman] No, that is not the direction
we want to take things in.
[Paris] Sorry to intrude.
I was going to invite the seniors
from the bowling alley out for lunch.
Would you make us a pasta dish?
Hmm…
[Paris] Diego, you're a chef?
Does this sound possible? Can you do it?
Yeah.
Of course we can, Paris.
[Paris] Great. I'll give them a call.
There are ten of us.
I believe the kitchen should have
what you need for a carbonara,
which would be great, okay?
See you later and thank you so much.
Ha!
[pan sizzling]
E-Excuse me.
Do you mind, please?
Huh?
No, no, I can't work like this.
I need some space around me to work.
[sighs]
I have very precise rules in my kitchen
and I can't work like this.
Look, I told him strips,
and he makes me cubes.
[Armando] I cut them in short strips.
They're in short strips!
If you're going to complain,
at least look.
[Diego] Pour! Come on!
That's better. Come on!
Fuck you!
-Confirmed.
-[Diego] Leave some water in, huh?
Ten seniors
ranging in age from 78 to 86.
[Diego] Okay, okay!
Let's turn it off now, huh?
Will you please stop touching things?
Come on! How much pasta is that?
Eight hundred grams.
I told you no more than 600.
I told you.
That is too much.
It's obviously too much.
No, no, it's okay.
[Diego] Over here.
The chef is over here.
It's too much.
Fucking hell! [gasps]
Sorry. Hmm. I told them
to fuck off twice already.
Susanna, don't worry
about swearing at two old bowlers.
It's terrible.
Uh, terrible? How?
It's just awful food.
There isn't enough s-seasoning
for the pasta. Forget it!
-Move it.
-Forget it!
Everyone leave me alone.
Okay? Please?
Leave me alone. I can't do this.
[man laughs]
Oh…
-Delicious.
-Huh! It's awful, it's awful.
-It's delicious.
-[Diego] Awful.
This is what you do.
You go all crazy like you can't do it,
when in fact, you made
a freakin' great dish!
-Try some, Chip.
-Oh, oh, I just had a crack... cracker.
-Double?
-Ugh!
Gina, here.
See? It's delicious.
-Tell him.
-[Diego groans]
See? Hmm, really good.
We are now serving pasta from the trash.
-What are you doing?
-We have to serve something.
What are you doing?
[groans loudly]
All right then. Then serve this!
Whoa! Stop it!
What are you doing?
You're not well.
Are you trying to burn me?
I would say no! Uh…
-Chip, it's a secret, okay?
-Yes.
[Clara] Gina, come on.
Help me out.
Come on.
Two plates!
Take this one too.
Okay.
[Clara sighs]
[man 1] Oh, oh!
[man 2] It's very nice.
[indistinct chatter]
Clara, Diego, come here!
Come on.
[Diego clears throat]
[indistinct chatter]
[Paris] It's very good.
-[Clara] Yes?
-We're going to do it every day.
How so?
Well, no one out there is paid
to understand or listen to you,
to hear all about the traumas
and the whys and the hows.
So, now the outside will come inside,
so you have the opportunity
to demonstrate that you're able
to interact with us.
So, let's stop with all the bread
and open up to the public.
[Chip] A restaurant?
Ha! They want us to open a restaurant.
Exactly. A very simple thing, no?
We have the cook already,
unless you're not feeling up to it.
[Susanna] Whoo!
And, Clara, since you claim
you have nothing to do around here…
[Clara] Mm-hmm.
…you'd be perfectly suited to run it.
-[Chip] Ha!
-But why me?
I don't want to run the group.
I'm made for something different
than the kitchen.
Why can't you do it?
Don't you want to leave?
Convince me to let you out.
Diego, maybe tomorrow
you'll make us a nice risotto?
[Chip] Ha!
-[indistinct chatter]
-Hmm…
I… I do only one dish a day, okay?
Only one.
Not a risotto and a main course.
I'm supposed to make them a dessert too?
[Clara] All right, all right.
-And you follow my rules, okay?
-Yes, okay.
-You do things my way.
-I get it. Why are you picking on me?
Because… because it sounds
pretty crazy, okay?
-Okay.
-This thing is idiotic.
You could've told him no.
Instead, you said yes.
I was saying no.
Wasn't I saying that I'm not, uh, able?
I don't know, I don't know,
but don't freak out on me, okay?
-Don't freak out on me.
-Turn here, turn here.
It's here, here.
-[Clara] Here?
-[Diego] Here.
[Clara] Okay.
[distant dog barking]
[Clara chuckles]
And here we are.
Hmm.
-[Diego clears throat]
-[Clara chuckles]
-You're pretty lost to the fairies.
-[Diego chuckles]
[both chuckle]
-Hmm… [laughs]
-Oh, my goodness!
She's one to talk, the fire-setter!
She's one to talk! [laughs]
[gulps]
Is that what they say?
What's that? [gulps]
That I burn down houses?
Oh, I completely wrecked a… a hotel.
Completely.
I wouldn't be offended if someone told--
-Get out! Just get out of my car!
-Okay.
-Go! Get out!
-I'm taking off the seat belt.
-Just leave!
-I'm getting my stuff.
And…
-I'm off.
-My husband was sick.
Oh.
He had a tumor.
Uh…
I sat with him every day and night.
Day and night.
[sighs deeply]
I fell asleep just one time, once,
and I was holding a cigarette.
The curtains caught fire.
It was an accident.
[trembling voice]
It was a goddamn accident.
[Diego] Hmm…
Oh, fuck! Huh?
Hmm… Did he die?
Your husband?
No. My husband wasn't hurt at all.
Oh.
But after all the things
I had done for him,
all the chemo,
the hospitals,
after that whole ordeal,
he got better.
He dumped me, just like that.
Oh…
Dumped me.
-[Diego sniffs]
-I was so stressed.
Things were bad.
-Hmm.
-And then I was dumped.
[Clara sighs, sniffs]
Now they say
I set houses on fire, you know?
[soft piano music playing]
It's just that people,
they don't really care.
And you… you're left alone.
I mean, really alone.
I know.
Mm-hmm.
-[Clara sighs softly]
-[Diego chuckles]
It's like you said earlier today,
if someone is sick,
then people are afraid.
It's like that.
Hmm…
[chuckles softly]
Thank you
for the ride.
[Clara inhales deeply]
Can I come up?
To use the bathroom?
[Diego gasps]
What are you asking?
I'm asking to come inside.
Hmm, hmm… Go inside?
Yeah.
You want…
What?
Are you going to take
the first guy who comes along?
No, I have to pee, like I said!
[Clara scoffs]
Don't get out.
You can't go up there.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
What do you think?
-[urinating]
-[Diego] Everyone here knows me!
[distant dog barking]
You're just
crazy!
[computer chimes]
CONGRATULATIONS!
WE'RE PLEASED TO INFORM YOU
THAT YOUR REQUEST HAS BEEN ACCEPTED
AND YOUR RESTAURANT
IS NOW VISIBLE ON OUR WEBSITE
[computer keys clicking]
[Clara] "It's at the edge of imagination,
the place where madness meets genius,
that you can experience
the most amazing, most delicious food
your palate has ever tasted."
[Chip] I have my own problems.
Hey! I… I have aliens to deal with.
If I'm not careful, they'll take my mom.
But I'm not gonna tell you that!
[Clara] "There's madness in the daring
menu of a chef who will surely get a star,
madness in the presentation of the dishes,
madness in the jazz
that plays late into the night,
when at last, it's time for a final glass
of that sweet elixir of Bacchus."
[Diego] This fridge is a mess.
It's a mess!
Okay, so, green v-vegetables
go on the b-bottom,
the other v-vegetables,
put them in the m-middle,
and cauliflower and the like
goes on top for obvious reasons.
[Clara] "Madness in the service…"
I'll prepare the liquid supply. Over.
"…that will literally leave you
speechless."
"This little gem is hidden away
in a secret location
whose address is revealed only
when a reservation has been made
in order to guarantee customers
the utmost confidentiality
and exclusivity."
What is that? What… what is that?
No, I… I mean,
this puts my mind at ease.
-Huh?
-These are our true selves.
You know, free, they're… free.
-This puts you at ease? Really?
-Uh, yes.
This calms you down because you're crazy.
Regular humans don't find this comforting.
-They find it horrifying.
-This is the truth, my truth.
What truth is that?
What truth are you talking about?
Get rid of it!
-[Double] No, this is my truth!
-No, it's not the truth. Get rid of it!
Don't you dare! This is my truth.
Inside of you is a part of me!
-Enough, Double!
-Inside of you--
Get rid of it!
-Get rid of this crap!
-My name is Armando!
[Clara gasps]
Leave it!
[Clara] "Maybe you've had a horrible day."
"Maybe you hate your coworkers,
or feel like you're the only real person
left on the face of the Earth,
…but the moment you cross
the threshold of the Monroe,
this magical place
will set you right in the world,
surprising you with its welcoming spirit,
its warmth,
and the breathtaking charm of its owner."
[computer chimes]
D-Do you like it?
-I do.
-Ah!
Thanks.
Hmm, let me help.
[indistinct background chatter]
Hmm.
[cell phone chimes]
Excuse me, Papa.
[Diego] Hmm.
Oh, it's Mom.
Wh-whose phone is that?
It's mine. It was a gift.
Honey, but you're too little
to have a cell phone.
Uh…
Who gave it to you? Your mom?
Well…
They chose it together.
Huh.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Uh, you're a social worker, right?
Okay, so, tell me,
do you think it's socially normal
for a girl who's only ten years old
to have a cell phone?
Sir, if your wife has
full custody of your daughter,
she makes the decisions.
No, but she didn't b-buy it.
The idiot did.
If you please, this is my daughter.
No, he shouldn't decide
whether she has her own cell phone.
Am I right?
-Yes. Calm down.
-[Diego] It's me!
-Take it easy.
-Stay calm.
Maybe if it was her mother.
-Not him.
-Calm down.
-Keep calm.
-[Diego] Not him. He's nobody!
Nobody!
[breathes heavily]
Uh…
Honey…
I'm sorry.
Look,
I didn't mean to.
I must… have… dropped it.
I… just dropped it.
Diego, Diego, I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it.
Paris says I create a hostile environment.
Me. Do you think
I create a hostile environment?
-What's wrong?
-Diego!
Hmm…
Uh…
You broke into the house
and destroyed everything.
-What are you doing here?
-You said you didn't have a key.
-You shouldn't be here.
-Leave me alone. I'll call the police!
-I haven't done anything.
-You'll never see Bianca again!
-It's breaking and entering.
-I haven't done anything.
[woman] You closed the door
with your three freakin' bolts!
Really, what a stupid, fake theft!
I saw right through it.
I think you were the one
who locked three bolts,
which is how it should be done.
The only things broken were Damiano's.
How did that happen?
So, he's definitely moved into our house,
you're saying?
He's living in our house with Bianca?
-No, no. You don't have a say.
-Say it.
You will not see Bianca.
-Not even with social services.
-No, don't say that to me!
Don't tell me I can't see her!
No, don't say it!
-Well, I'm saying it.
-Don't say it.
[Clara] What's going on?
Clara, please, n-not right now.
This madman broke into my house
this morning and destroyed everything!
That can't be because Diego slept over
at my house last night and we woke up at…
What was it, Peanut, 11:00?
So, then, no, Diego couldn't have done it.
Oh, no, what if it was burglars?
Maybe they stole something.
Also, he told me
he doesn't have a key anymore.
It would be upsetting
if I found out he still did.
-Hmm, hmm…
-Did you sleep with her?
Huh?
-Hmm, hmm…
-Babe, you didn't tell her?
-Uh…
-I'm sorry. Who are you?
-[Diego sighs]
-Clara.
-And you must be Diana.
May I call you Diana?
They fuck hard!
-Susanna!
-[Susanna] Sorry.
You whore!
Oh!
-Excuse her. She has Tourette's.
-Oh.
I've been involved
with the process of rehabilitation.
I come in once a week
to create, let's say, a sort of continuity
between everyday life
and life at the center.
Right, my love?
Uh, I guess there was a chance
that I was the one who closed it perhaps.
I've been a little stressed out lately.
I… I'm gonna go.
I'm glad you're doing so well.
-Excuse me.
-[Clara chuckles]
-[Clara] Ciao, Diana.
-Ciao.
You broke into her house.
-You lie just like a professional.
-No. Don't use that word.
The point is she thinks you have changed
and you're with a nice, super cool girl.
It's been ten years
since she apologized to me.
You're welcome.
But everyone in there is so boring.
And so old.
I know, but you have to look
on the bright side.
[distant shouting and chatter]
Ten tokens for you.
What? The bright side?
Sure, you and me
are having fun today.
[children laughing]
["Yes Sir, I Can Boogie"
by Baccara playing]
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
[inaudible speech]
Quack, quack! Quack, quack!
-Quack, quack!
-Quack, quack, quack!
Quack, quack, quack!
♪ Mister ♪
♪ Your eyes are full of hesitation ♪
♪ Sure makes me wonder… ♪
[screaming and laughter]
♪ If you know what you're looking for… ♪
Whoo! [laughs]
♪ Baby… ♪
Look, you do everything with this pedal.
You step down to accelerate,
take your foot off to brake.
-Okay?
-But… but I'm afraid.
You don't have to be afraid.
Just pretend that's the guy
in the nursing home and just, bang!
-[woman laughs]
-Go after him just like this!
♪ Yes, sir, I can boogie ♪
Bang!
♪ But I need a certain song ♪
♪ I can boogie ♪
♪ Boogie-boogie… ♪
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
-I'll be right back!
-Whoa!
Whoa!
[laughs loudly]
I'm going to get us more tokens, okay?
Just one minute!
Move!
I'll be right back!
Anna?
♪ Yes, sir, I can boogie ♪
♪ But I need a…  ♪
Where did she go?
♪ I can boogie ♪
♪ Boogie-boogie… ♪
Anna?
We need another ten tokens, please.
[tokens jangle]
[man laughing]
[woman groans]
Adelaide!
What's she doing?
-Stop it! Adelaide! Hey!
-[Adelaide groaning]
Adelaide, what happened?
Help us out!
What's wrong?
The doctor says to take it easy.
It's only a small wrist fracture.
Okay? Hmm?
You gave her a complete checkup?
Everything's fine?
[man] Hello.
Afternoon.
-De Pascalis.
-Afternoon.
I'm the director of her nursing home.
-Tell me what happened.
-Nothing!
Just like I already told you
a thousand times,
we were calmly, the lady and I,
sitting quietly on a bench
when all of a sudden, boom, she falls.
I don't know if she hit her head or what,
so I take her in for a CAT scan,
just to be certain
she doesn't get to the nursing home
only to have a vein explode in her head,
and then she drops dead
over some silly bullshit!
Adelaide, did you really fall
getting up from your seat?
[Adelaide breathes deeply]
It was a… such a wonderful day.
I had so much fun today.
[Adelaide chuckles]
If you would come with me
to sign her discharge papers?
I don't understand how an elderly person
can be entrusted with someone like that.
-It was a judge's order.
-Clara…
You keep putting yourself in situations
that make it hard to defend you.
And you should take off
that little bracelet.
[distant siren wailing]
[footsteps]
Ciao.
Hey, so, did you know
that Susanna has been going around saying,
"They fuck hard, they fuck hard"?
And now everyone in here thinks
you and I are some kind of couple.
Everyone, everyone.
So what?
Well, so, this information
has reached Paris, right?
Tell me why I should care about Paris.
Two more meatballs. They fuck hard!
-Huh?
-[Susanna] Sorry.
-She told four old guys to fuck off!
Not my fault. I don't do it on purpose.
You don't do it on purpose, but you do it.
Fuck off to you too, okay?
She's like this all day long.
She goes around saying, "They fuck hard!"
to the whole center.
If I may say so, it's perfectly normal
that it bothers me, no?
I mean, if my reaction--
Oh!
Does it seem normal
that every time you make a huge mess,
I have to save your ass, then you say
you don't want this going around?
-You are crazy!
-What did you say?
-Stop it!
-You called me crazy?
-Calm… calm down.
Yeah.
I am not crazy!
I am not… crazy!
Do you understand?
[sobbing] I'm not fucking crazy!
I've had a bad day!
And I'm tired!
Someone has a hard day.
No, don't help them.
Tell them that they're crazy!
Tell her that she's mad!
[Clara panting]
[sobbing] I had a really difficult day.
[melancholic music playing]
[Clara continues sobbing]
Uh…
Hmm…
[Diego inhales deeply]
[Clara sobs softly]
Hmm… Um…
[Clara whimpers]
[Clara gulps]
[Clara sobs]
[horn blares]
Hmm…
I…
I don't really believe you're crazy.
N… not in any clinical sense, I mean.
-[chuckles]
-Aha!
Oh, that's funny.
[chuckling] I know.
Coming from the man
who broke into his wife's apartment.
No. No.
-Hmm, yeah.
-No, no, no, no.
-Yes.
-That house is m-mine!
That other guy is staying at my house!
In my bedroom,
in my… bed, using my nightstand,
and he gets to wake up at home
with my daughter instead of me?
You're right.
-Somehow I'm the one doing the violating?
-Calm down. Calm down.
Calm down. You're right.
[Diego] It makes me crazy.
I'm so… afraid that… Bianca
is going to forget me.
[melancholic music playing]
My mother, when I was four years old,
up and left.
She disappeared overnight
and I never saw her again.
I don't even remember
the face of my own mother!
My father has 300 photos,
but there's… not… one
of my mother!
One thing I do remember,
she was always singing, always.
♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Just you and nobody else… ♪
Marilyn.
Uh, Marilyn?
Marilyn Monroe.
-[thunder rumbles]
-[Diego] Quella.
Oh…
I mean, I don't want
the same thing to happen to Bianca,
that she forgets… my face, you know?
[distant horn blares]
[emotive music playing]
-Fuck, it's pouring.
-Yeah, it is.
Over there!
[Clara giggles]
You're soaking wet!
[both laugh]
Soaking!
[both continue laughing]
It's pouring down.
[Clara laughs]
Oh!
-Your phone is ringing.
-[Clara] Oh.
-Yeah.
-[cell phone vibrating]
Hmm.
[music stops]
Hello?
Good evening.
Uh… Yes.
Uh… No, I'm sorry.
I believe we're all booked up
for the next six weeks.
Yeah.
No.
Of course, of course!
Yes, please call back.
We'll be waiting. Good night.
Hmm, nothing.
What do you m-mean,
booked up for six weeks?
-What is?
-Nothing.
Are you… pulling my leg?
I was standing right here.
I might have written a few…
A few?
…reviews on a page I made on the Internet
of a restaurant that doesn't exist,
but like our restaurant if it did.
Right, so, are you making up things
about the cooking lab?
Doesn't sound great put that way.
Wait.
Hang on. Take a look.
"The Monroe is like being
in the Village in New York,
a marvelous, classy place
that needs no travel
because it's right in the center."
Was that written by you?
No, I didn't write it.
Someone else, who has never been there
before, after reading my reviews did.
Understand?
No, no.
So, basically, people write these reviews
without ever setting foot
in the restaurant.
And then I'm bombarded
with calls to make reservations,
but I always tell them that we're busy.
-But how can you do that?
-It's easy.
-No, no, no.
-Yes, yes, yes.
-You can't do that.
-Yes, I can.
-My God!
-Paris asked us to run a restaurant.
He didn't tell us we couldn't fantasize.
And pretending feels good to me.
[jazz music playing]
[doorbell rings]
Come in. It's open.
May I?
[Clara] Yes, come in!
Okay.
[door closes]
-Come in.
-[Diego] Ciao.
[Clara] Have a seat.
We've gotten over a thousand emails.
What emails?
For the restaurant, the Monroe.
Uh, no, then leave out that "we" part.
Okay.
Anyway, we went all the way
from last place
to 1,500th place In three days.
Wow!
[Clara chuckles softly] Hmm.
[Clara chuckles]
How come Monroe?
Thank you for reminding me.
So, basically, I had this relative.
She was my Russian second aunt, right?
And at some point,
she opened her own restaurant in Russia,
where she was performing
almost every night.
She was identical to Marilyn Monroe.
By an absurd combination of genes,
I look exactly like my aunt.
At auditions,
they tell me I look just like Marilyn.
So I thought, "I'll call it the Monroe."
Actually, M-Marilyn had
blonde hair and light eyes.
No, a brunette who went blonde,
raised her forehead and got a nose job.
-She was blonde with light eyes.
-No, no.
If you just think about it,
you can't tell from the photos.
In fact, she had black eyes
and a mole that was drawn in.
-If you watch the movies, you can tell.
-It was all fake.
Watch the movies.
Do you have to shave your armpits?
[Diego laughs]
[Clara] No, I make the dishes
to photograph.
-Oh, with shaving cream?
-[Clara] Yeah.
[jazz music playing]
That's fake food?
-[Clara] Mm-hmm.
-[Diego] Really? All of it?
[Clara] Hmm.
My God!
Impressive.
I learned it
from an artist friend.
I w-wouldn't put those berries there.
[camera clicks]
Beautiful.
This one isn't as good as the other one.
-Which one?
-This one.
Uh… Ah, because it's a little empty.
-[Clara] It's just too much white.
-Yeah, it would need something like…
-[Clara] What should we use?
-What is that?
[Clara] It's like a paint.
Uh, no, it would be a mousse,
a salmon mousse.
Okay, how do we make a salmon mousse?
Uh, we'll use your foot.
-No.
-Yes.
-We're not using my foot.
-I'll put the egg on your foot.
[Clara] You're not putting an egg
on my foot. Use your foot.
-My foot is hairy.
-No!
Put your foot there.
Please put down your foot.
All right, tell me where to put it.
Why don't you lean towards the light?
Right.
-[Clara] Like that?
-[Diego] Yes.
-[Clara] Gross.
-[Diego] Don't move.
-[Diego] Ah!
-[Clara chuckles]
-[Clara] Gross.
-Okay.
-[chuckles] Ew!
-[Clara] Are you taking it?
-Don't move.
-[Clara] All right.
-[Diego] Don't move.
-Like that?
-Yes, stay right where you are.
-Good.
-How does it look?
-[chuckles] Oh, my God!
-[Diego laughs]
Impressive.
-Yes.
-Incredible.
[Clara giggles]
Let's use this one.
[tapping keys] Okay.
[crunching]
And then this one.
Hey, how do you see me?
I mean, not really you.
In the abstract, in general.
-[Diego] Hmm…
-As a woman, like…
What do you think?
Well,
I… I don't know.
I mean, I suppose
you're someone that appears skinny,
then up close, if you look carefully,
I mean, you have a big ass, no?
Wh-what exactly do you do?
BEST LEADING ACTRESS
-A little bit of it all.
-[Diego] Oh.
Uh, commercials,
a little film, television.
Oh, but I haven't ever seen you.
Oh, well, um…
[inhales deeply]
I can show you
the last thing I did. Come here.
One minute.
[taps key]
Are you watching carefully?
None of this here…
Yes.
None of this
would've been possible before right now.
Right now, though…
Right now…
it is.
This shoot, it was for a Korean director
in a studio
that was just rebuilt in Germany,
in East Berlin.
-How fun!
-[Clara chuckles]
How come I haven't seen this one either?
That makes sense. Yeah.
Because, well,
I made it for the Asian market,
so, you wouldn't have seen it.
[Diego] Oh… [chuckles]
[both laugh]
-Play it one more time, can you?
-Sure.
-No, no. No, no, no, sweetheart.
-Yes, yes!
-No, no.
-Yes!
-Just look!
-Uh…
He says it's a really fancy place
with waiters in black.
It's called the Monroe, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, of course.
I… I work there.
-Yes--
-Look. There's your picture.
See?
Oh…
[Diego breathes anxiously]
"The chef is one of the rare cases
on the Roman scene
with substance and class all in one."
Who's the chef?
Uh… I am.
I'm… I'm… I'm the chef.
That sounds really cool!
Maybe I can go there with you to see it.
Well,
that's…
um…
Bianca told me th-that she wants
to see where… where  I work.
What am I gonna do?
I can't bring her here!
Hmm… No.
No, no,
of course you can't bring her here.
[Diego sniffs]
-[sniffs]
-Tell her some bullshit.
I'll take your picture
and photoshop it like this.
-Isn't this one beautiful?
-I can't. I'm not like you.
I'm not comfortable just telling her
some crap while looking into her eyes.
I feel like a monster. A monster, okay?
Okay. Okay. Do whatever you want to do.
I don't need to help you.
Once in a while, you have to do
something you don't want to do
to resolve a situation, okay?
[Diego sighs]
[sniffs]
Uh, uh…
Uh…
We could open up f-for real.
-Uh…
-[Clara] What?
The Monroe. Uh…
What do you mean?
We can put the address on your site
and open… open up the Monroe,
so Bianca can come in.
-That won't work.
-Yes, it will.
No, it won't work.
The Monroe doesn't exist.
If you put down the address, it exists.
Not only does it not exist,
the Monroe is mine.
It's mine, the Monroe.
Bianca might actually be proud
of something I've done, you know?
But proud of what, of what, of what?
That this place sucks?
The Monroe doesn't exist. It's not open.
That's the end of it. All right? Okay?
And fuck me
for telling you about the site!
Sure, because you… you…
you're a big… big talker,
but when it comes time
for doing anything, you chicken out, huh?
-You're only capable of this… this shit!
-Whoa!
Because you're a bald-faced liar.
-You're a bald-faced liar!
-What do you want?
You're the one shitting himself
over losing your daughter! You!
-Not me!
-Fuck, fuck you!
Fuck you, fuck you!
-Fuck you!
-Whoa!
Pick this shit up.
[Diego breathing heavily]
-[Diego screams]
-No!
What are you doing?
[water hissing]
[Clara] Great.
Well done.
Calm and collected.
A perfect gentleman like always.
[Diego] What are you doing?
That rag won't help.
I'm at least doing something.
[Diego] Well, isn't there, like, a clamp,
something like that?
Yes, probably in that drawer over there.
If Paris sees it, we're fucked.
You asshole!
-[Diego] Let me do it.
-Oh, sure, the plumber!
-[hissing]
-Hurry!
[Diego] It's… it's the valve.
[grunting with exertion]
-Ugh!
-Oh!
♪ I was working in my lab… ♪
[Clara screams]
♪ When my monster from his slab
Began to rise ♪
♪ And then suddenly to my surprise ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ He did the monster mash ♪
♪ The monster mash ♪
♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ It caught on in a flash ♪
♪ The monster mash ♪
♪ He did the monster mash ♪
♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ We got it on in a flash ♪
♪ The monster mash ♪
♪ He did the monster mash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ The monster mash ♪
♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪Yeah, we got it on in a flash ♪
♪The monster mash ♪
♪ He did the monster mash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
[Double] You ruined the mural!
-Okay, Armando…
-[Susanna] Fuck you!
-It is not ruined.
-They're coming.
Yes, 20 centimeters of water,
then all that splashing!
Fuck you, fuck you!
-Fuck you!
-Okay, just calm down.
-[Double] You're happy about it.
-No, I'm not happy!
-[all talking at once]
-Okay, okay, okay, everybody stay calm!
[Chip] I hope they're okay with it all.
[chair scraping]
This is what life is like.
There are frustrations
and you have to deal with them.
Gina, stop moving around, for God's sake!
[Chip] Ha!
All right, can we try to stay quiet?
And listen to how we feel inside.
[Double sighs]
Chip, please, go ahead.
Okay, well, my job has been lost.
And it's creating
quite a bit of anxiety for me.
Clara, you find this funny?
Well, he lost his job for four days
while everything dries
and we get a break.
I'd say it's more of a relief.
[Diego] That's crazy.
I mean, three years,
that's how long you've been here
and… you can't even sit in the circle.
[breathing heavily]
-What does that matter?
-Huh?
-It does matter!
-It does! It matters!
-They fuck hard!
[Susanna panting]
Diego, you seem nervous and mad too.
Can we please not go there?
Well, you see,
if we don't go there,
then we don't realize
that everyone here has something to lose.
[Diego] N-no.
There are those who have nothing to lose
b-because some people have nothing.
He's wrong. In fact, everyone in that lab
has something important.
What's important?
[Paris] For example, themselves,
the chance to do something different,
something personal and shared.
So, basically, everything.
[Diego sighs]
[Diego sighs, clicks tongue]
[indistinct TV commentary]
Can you make it 15 or 19, please,
not 17?
Thank you.
[doorbell rings]
[Diego's dad eating noisily]
Who's that?
-Don't know.
-[doorbell rings]
I'm not going.
[knock at door]
[Diego] Who is it?
[shouting] Who is it?
Clara.
What do you want?
[Clara] Open up.
Why should I?
[thumping on door]
Okay, I'm opening, I'm opening.
I'm… I'm opening!
-Hmm!
-Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no, no, no. You can't come in.
-Evening.
You live with your dad?
It's a temporary situation.
I am being bombarded with calls.
Some guy called three times in one day.
I told him we were full until Christmas.
He asked to make a reservation that night.
Christmas!
And… so what?
[Clara sighs]
And so…
And so… it's yes?
We're opening!
You know we are making a huge mistake?
Hey, hey, hey.
-Do you trust me?
-No.
-Do you trust yourself?
-What are these questions?
-No, I don't trust myself.
-Bad, very bad. You should.
Only three problems, as far as I can see.
One,  is it called Mon- roe or Mon-roe?
Mon-roe. Its name is Mon-roe.
[Diego] Hmm.
Okay. Two, I make one dish per day.
Not two. One.
Three, what do we do about those who are--
Nothing. We tell them nothing.
-They don't need to know anything.
-But people are assholes.
They'll treat them terribly.
Right.
I want to start with a carbonara…
[Clara] "Do you ever feel overwhelmed
by the inability to communicate?"
"Yes, the inability to communicate."
"That ugly thing that takes hold of us
and makes us feel tremendously alone?"
CLOSED DUE TO FLOODING
"That makes the suffering
of others seem so frightening?"
"You know I'm telling the truth."
"We find other people's suffering scary,
and we don't even know the reason why."
Can someone tell me…
"Perhaps we think that hiding from it
means it won't affect us."
Should we try to turn it on?
Wow!
Cool, huh?
Hey, Chip!
Wh-what are you staring at, huh? Huh?
We made a couple changes.
[Chip grumbles]
I'm noticing suspicious behavior
in the restaurant. I repeat…
To me, I don't know why,
but it's beautiful.
I mean, it's a real look.
It says something profound.
-Fuck you, shithead!
-Armando!
-[Susanna laughs]
-[Armando] Thank you.
Why don't you paint this area too, huh?
That way,
you can really unleash your talents.
But this time, use some color.
Fuck you!
[Clara shrieks]
[Clara] "With this in mind,
we offer a new collective experience
from the Monroe
in which the most disruptive performances
contemporary art has to offer
is combined with the usual refinement
of flavor that our chef is known for."
"Each night comes
with its own unique dish, the absolute."
"The artist Gina brings the question
of our inability to communicate to life,
showcasing the deep loneliness
of humanity."
I'm just tidying up here.
[Clara] "In the figurative art space,
the murals painted by Double
force us to answer the question,
"Are our true selves really here,
or somewhere else, happy and free?"
"A dialogue both desired and denied
is staged nightly by the artist Chip."
"And if you're lucky enough
to be served by Susanna,
you'll be treated to a performance
that will make you ponder the violence
and sexualization of modern life."
You know that if we publish the address,
then people
will really actually come here, right?
That seems like the whole purpose, no?
[chuckles softly] Okay.
Why don't you do it?
"So, instead of running scared,
for one night, let your other self out,
the stranger, the madman."
"Whoever it is, let them join us
for an experience like no other."
-Don't worry.
-[Clara] "Maybe you'll discover…"
Don't worry.
"…that the madman is
much closer to your real self
than you've ever imagined."
-Mission accomplished.
-[Clara] Okay.
I'm turning everything off.
-Oh!
-[Susanna] Fuck you!
[Chip chuckles nervously]
Turn the lights back on.
Turn the lights back on. Do you hear me?
Thank you. Ha!
[Clara breathes deeply]
["Always Alright"
by Alabama Shakes playing]
[Diego gulps]
♪ Well, you come upstairs
But not to talk ♪
♪ You stay a little while
Then you do a little walk on home…  ♪
[Chip] Oh!
Situation out of control.
I repeat, situation out of control.
I'll continue to be undercover,
but I'm going to need reinforcements.
♪ So you took me to the party
And got me to notice ♪
♪ That you wanna feel good
And you feel like you're gonna explode… ♪
[Chip] Oh!
[patrons chatting]
♪ Well, pass me the whiskey
Pass me the gin ♪
♪ Pass me
Whatever there's drink left in… ♪
Are you okay?
What's going on tonight?
Uh…
-Well, I don't know.
-Hmm…
Hmm… I don't think I can.
[breathes anxiously]
Can't I be in the kitchen
for just one night?
No.
It's so humiliating.
[Clara] Susanna…
Susanna, keep your head up, don't worry.
You have to stay calm.
And I guarantee
that tonight no one will mind.
-[Susanna] Oh…
-Just have fun. Okay?
-Hmm…
-Come on. Come on.
[chatting continues]
[rock music playing]
I guess carbonara for everyone.
What are we supposed to say?
Uh, you're supposed to order drinks.
-[Susanna laughs]
-Oh, right.
-Five beers.
-Fuck you, bastard! Fuck you!
Sorry.
Five beers.
They're incredible.
[Double] You're tricking us! Who knows
how many things you don't tell us?
It's all part of the performance.
Okay? Good.
You don't tell us! I know
there's something you aren't telling us!
What's going on?
-I've seen it all!
-[Clara] What are you doing?
[Diego] What are you talking about?
You're out of your mind!
-What's happening?
-He didn't put salt in the water.
Diego got angry.
He didn't do it because there's a plot.
There's something you're not telling us,
and I'm gonna talk to Paris!
Don't you dare go anywhere near Paris.
-Okay?
-[Clara] Calm down.
No, calm down!
[Chip crying]
-Leave… leave him alone!
-I want my mom!
-I have seen it all!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I've read it all!
There's a site on the Internet.
-And you're all scheming!
-[Chip] Mama!
I want my mommy! Don't kill me!
-I wanna see my mom again!
-Calm down. Give me that.
-[Clara] Look at me.
-I want my mommy!
-Look at me.
-[Diego] Stay calm.
Look at me. Look at me.
Uh… Thank you.
What, have you lost your damn mind?
-He's threatening me!
-No, no, I'm not!
-I'm not!
There's a plot. I am not out of my mind.
I am totally lucid.
Lucid? You were holding
a giant knife! Jesus!
-It's Paris!
-[Clara] Fuck!
-[Susanna] He heard the screams.
-Call Paris. Tell him Diego threatened me.
-These are my witnesses.
-I'll give testimony.
Not true! It's not true!
Susanna, stop, stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
Stop it!
-There's a conspiracy.
-[Chip] Yes.
No, there is no conspiracy!
All we did was put out
a little publicity. Okay?
-Yeah.
-[Diego] Okay?
-[Clara] Yeah.
-Just a little bit of publicity. Okay?
To earn…
Uh, uh, to earn some money
to travel to Papua New Guinea…
so we can all be free.
-[Chip] Ha!
-[Diego] Okay?
-Uh, to… to be free?
-To be free, yes.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, yeah.
-You see?
-You're sure?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yes. It's true.
-[Diego] See?
-Diego's telling the truth.
So, that's enough bullshit.
And now this group of crazy people
are going to gang up on… everybody.
Are you w-with me?
We're all a team, huh?
There's a lot of people out there,
and we need to make a great impression.
It's exactly the kind of thing
that Paris wants to see,
is for us to make
a great impression, okay?
Great.
Okay, so, the pasta doesn't have salt
and it's freezing.
Just put some salt on it now.
Or just fix it again.
-It'll take ten minutes.
-Impossible.
-But why?
-We don't have any more pasta. Done.
Nobody expected
this many people to be here.
-I have another 20 orders.
-Go buy some more for us.
-I go?
-Yes, you go.
-Now? Without cover?
-Yes.
-Ha!
Armando, make me a strawberry mirepoix.
-A what?
-Just chop the strawberries.
[Clara] That's what I do when I forget.
I put salt on it and go.
That's not salt. It's sugar. They start…
They're starting at the finish,
with dessert.
Okay. Gina, go out there in the hall
and manage the situation.
You're gonna be fine. Don't worry. Go.
-[Diego] Okay.
-[Double] What's next?
[Diego] Next, we're gonna take off
some leaves.
There, that's perfect.
Yeah, and now…
Cream. Cream, cream, cream, cream.
Coffee.
Cream. Hmm…
He's doing his thing.
W-watch.
Strawberry and… biscotti. And voilà!
-Who wants to taste?
-Jump into the void. No time.
Susanna, Susanna, now you go out
and say that this is an exclusive evening.
We present our dinner "au contraire."
Okay?
Not with that expression.
Be confident, calm.
Believe in it and they will too,
I promise. Understand? Hmm?
Au contraire, au contraire.
Let's go, let's go! Go!
-Go!
-Hmm.
Okay, we can do this!
Come on. Yes, we can make it work.
We can make it work.
Hmm.
-Oh!
-[Diego] Yeah?
Bravo.
[rock music playing]
[patrons chatting]
Can you tell me what's going on?
Marketing.
It's the outside coming inside,
and we're managing it, no?
Dinner… au contraire.
May I say something?
-[Diego] Yes.
-Dinner was incredible. Our compliments.
Thank you.
-It was great.
-Thank you.
Good night. Hmm.
[indistinct background chatter]
[Diego sighs softly]
Hey.
[Diego] Hmm…
What's up?
[Clara sighs]
[Diego] Hey.
Do you realize we made it work?
We really did it!
[Clara chuckles]
[both chuckle]
[cheerful music playing]
-[Diego] Where are we going?
-[Clara] Sh! Keep quiet!
Here, here!
-Are you sure?
-Sh!
Phew!
Follow me.
[clanking]
Put your leg through first. Come on!
I'm pretty sure
this is illegal.
Of course it's illegal.
-Well, of course it's illegal.
-Come on.
Come on! I've done this a million times
and I've only got caught once.
Only once?
Wow!
This is enormous!
[Clara laughs] Oh!
[Clara giggles]
Wow! Oh!
[Clara] Five, four,
three, two,
one, zero!
I'm gonna find you right away!
-[Diego laughs]
-[Clara] No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[Clara and Diego laughing loudly]
-[Diego] You lose!
-[Clara] Stop!
I'm exhausted.
[Diego] Whoo! Uh…
[Clara laughs]
[Diego sighs]
Uh, you know…
y-you're a genius.
Why's that?
[Diego] Uh, because you came up
with a totally crazy idea,
and look what happened.
-[Clara chuckles]
-And look what you got out of me!
I mean, can you believe it?
-[Diego laughs]
-Well…
It wasn't my idea.
I read it in a magazine
about someone who had done it in London.
Really?
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh.
Well, uh, but you did a…
[Clara sighs]
[Diego] …a really good job.
And even with my husband,
it didn't go exactly like I told you.
-Oh, it didn't?
-My husband worked in finance.
And he was never home,
he was never around.
And he just ignored me and so, I just…
[chuckles]
…made up all kinds of stories.
Sometimes they were auditions,
or theater tours that never existed.
But I saw… the posters at your home.
All fake.
Y-you made them?
Hmm.
-All of… all of them?
-[Clara] All of them.
And then one day,
he came to see me at the theater.
[chuckles]
I, obviously, wasn't there.
So, when he came home that night,
I made a terrible scene.
I accused him of cheating on me
with a colleague, which wasn't even true.
I just wanted him…
…wanted him to see me
just for a moment, a moment.
And when people don't see you,
it's terrible.
[Clara] Really terrible.
Then, when he said
he was breaking up with me,
I told him…
[chuckles] I don't even know
how it came to me, but I told him,
"If you break up with me,
I'll set fire to the curtains."
"One, two, three."
He looked at me with this face
as if to say, "Do it, come on!"
"Set them on fire, on fire."
Because if you don't,
you're not credible anymore, right?
-And so I had to set the curtains on fire.
-Sure.
-[Clara] Right, you know?
But then,
it wasn't just the curtains
that caught fire, it was the whole house,
and the house next door.
The neighbor was out, but his dog
was there and it burned to death.
-The dog burned to death.
-Oh, shit!
This is who I am.
[Clara sobs, sniffs]
I fucking suck!
I really suck.
N-no.
And there goes the magic!
Now you'll go away and leave me alone.
They think they're right
just because there are more of them.
Who?
Uh, well, the "normal" ones.
[Clara laughs]
L-let's do something.
Do you know what we're gonna do,
starting in this moment?
Be the good guys.
You're gonna stop… making up nonsense.
Come on. Yes, yes, listen.
And I will stop breaking things. Yeah?
Just between us, okay?
-[Clara inhales deeply]
-[Diego] Let's be good.
We'll try.
Okay, we know.
We know where… where we stand, no?
So, now, how about we go get a croissant?
[Clara chuckles softly]
A croissant.
[Diego] You want one?
-[Diego chuckles]
-Hmm.
[telephone rings]
["The Boy with the Arab Strap" playing]
Yes?
For eight?
Name?
Perfect. We'll see you then. Thanks.
[telephone rings]
Yes?
A birthday dinner? Okay. How many people?
♪ A mile and a half on a bus
Takes a long time ♪
♪ The odor of old prison food
Takes a long time to pass you by… ♪
[Susanna] About two hours.
I'm very sorry.
Fuck you, bastard, fuck you!
Yeah, we'll wait.
-I'll put you on the list. Name?
-Emanuel.
[Double grunting]
Gina! Gina!
-[Double] What are you doing?
-Shit!
-[Double] Coming in here to show us--
-[Clara] Gina! Help me!
-Get off me!
-Get up!
-He's the real me!
-Enough!
All part of the performance.
How extraordinary! Extraordinary!
-It's him!
-Outstanding!
Very good! Chip!
Didn't look like you for shit, Double!
Now I'm scared. It's too many people.
I'm scared. [breathes anxiously]
That's okay. It's normal.
It makes sense.
It's your first contact with the outside.
There's nothing to be afraid of here.
There's nothing threatening you.
It's a chance, Chip. An opportunity.
[Chip laughs]
-Oh God!
-We have a sponsor.
[chuckles] They sent us a lot of stuff.
Imagine that, huh?
Oh, great, boss!
I like "boss." [chuckles]
-It's out there. Go and get it.
-Uh-huh.
Oh, we've made the top 100 restaurants
in the city, out of 13,500.
♪ The man who drives minicabs
Down in Old Compton… ♪
13,501 to be precise.
I mean, this is unreal.
♪ A central location for you is a must ♪
♪ As you stagger about making free
With your lewd and lascivious boasts… ♪
We've had complaints
from people in the area.
Those are all old men
from the bowling alley.
Miss, you do realize
that you don't even have a permit
to play music here, right?
[Clara sighs]
What do you mean, we can't play music?
Okay, can I see your permit?
♪ Strapped to the table
With suits from the Shelter shop ♪
♪ Comic celebrity takes a back seat ♪
♪ As the cigarette catches… ♪
Hey.
[door closes]
[Clara] Look.
Did I mention that I'd handle it?
Look, you're welcome. I handled it.
Tonight… Bianca's coming.
That's great, no?
A little enthusiasm, please.
And today's menu?
[jazz music playing]
Pasta with tomato.
Pasta with tomato?
Sounds delicious.
[jazz music continues]
Ciao.
I made your favorite dinner.
[music drowns out speech]
[Diego] Thank you. Here's your table.
[patrons chatting]
All right. I'll be right back.
[jazz continues]
[instrumental break]
Thank you.
Thanks.
[jazz song resumes]
Delicious, Mom!
Enjoy your dinner. We'll be back soon.
[cheering]
[patrons chatting]
[Clara clears throat]
[feedback screeches]
Good evening, everybody.
Um, tonight, I'm singing a song
dedicated to a friend of mine,
um, because…
[Clara chuckles]
Well, because he knows why.
[musical introduction plays]
♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Just you… ♪
They're taking her away. Really,
they're taking her away. It's a signal.
♪ I wanna be loved you ♪
[out of tune] ♪ Alone… ♪
[snickering]
♪ I wanna be kissed by you ♪
♪ Just you, nobody else but you ♪
♪ Alone… ♪
♪ By you… ♪
[music continues playing]
Hey, what's up? Why did you stop?
-I was having a panic attack.
-[Diego] Wait!
Hey, look, that was very, very nice,
what you were doing.
-[Clara] No.
-Keep going.
If you don't, I will, so, it'll…
it'll be much worse, believe me.
[out of tune] ♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Just you and nobody else but you! ♪
♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Alone… ♪
-You see? Come on.
-No.
-Come on.
-Don't leave me there alone.
-No.
-Come on. Yes, yes, yes.
-Come on. How does it go?
-Please, don't. "I couldn't aspire."
-Huh?
-"I couldn't aspire."
♪ I couldn't aspire ♪
♪ To anything higher ♪
♪ Than to feel the desire ♪
♪ To make you my own ♪
♪ Own… ♪
[both laugh]
♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Just you and nobody else but you ♪
♪ I wanna be loved by you ♪
♪ Alone… ♪
[Clara giggles]
[cheering]
[both laugh]
I told you! Hmm…
It was a joke. Excuse me.
-[Susanna] Whoo! Whoo!
-Excuse me.
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Ha ha!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
[Susanna gasps]
[Clara laughs]
-Your singing's awful!
-Look who… who… who's talking!
[both laugh]
And what are you wearing, anyway?
And… and that hairpiece?
[Diego laughs loudly]
But…
But I made a real effort.
[Diego continues laughing]
-[Diego sighs]
-[Clara] Hmm.
[Diego laughs]
[distant swing music playing]
[Clara laughs]
I sang your song.
-No. No, no, no. I sang that song.
-I sang it too.
Well, it wasn't all me.
-But I sang it… more.
-But I sang it too.
I did.
[Diego] Hmm.
-Hmm.
-Oh God.
-I'm sorry. I thought…
-No, no.
Forget it.
Uh…
No, it's just, um…
Hmm…
Hmm, hmm…
It's… inappropriate.
No, no, for sure, we shouldn't…
Uh, sorry, but why shouldn't we?
-Because I'm pretty sure we should.
-Uh…
Uh…
Well, with all the
problems I have,
I mean, should I add you too?
Uh…
Oh, so, I'd just be another problem?
No, no, it's just I…
worry that if I'm with someone like you,
then Bianca will be taken…
taken away… from me.
[laughs nervously]
And I won't see her again.
And there's no review from the judge.
[Diego laughs nervously]
[Diego sighs]
[distant applause]
[Diego] Hmm.
Uh… Hmm.
-Asshole!
-Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Oh… Oh, fuck!
Uh…
God…
I'd like to speak to the manager, please.
[swing music playing]
I dimmed the lights,
and people started dancing.
Oh, and we have a problem over there.
And there.
There's three.
Evening. Is something wrong?
Hello. Good evening, miss.
Are you aware that playing music
in a restaurant requires a permit?
Can I see it?
Do you seriously think
we'd play music without a permit?
No, but I need to see it.
Of course we have the permit.
We wouldn't play without it.
I need to check it, miss.
Please find it for me.
Sorry, sir. We have the permit.
Go get it for him, okay?
I mean, we have it.
No, it bothers me
that someone doesn't trust me,
you know, because I'm a professional,
and I have it right here!
-Here!
-What happened to you?
Uh, I bumped my nose opening the door up.
Here it is.
Are you making a joke?
Making a joke? Why?
Because this document is fake.
Where did you get it?
It's a fake?
Yes, it's fake.
Okay, no more music in here.
Hey, guys,
get them to stop playing right now!
We're gonna check IDs now too.
You two, start checking IDs here.
Take care of them.
Don't give them your IDs.
Set an example
and be the first to show your ID.
-Don't give them your ID!
-Give me your identification now!
There's a fire!
-There's a fire! There's a fire!
-Fire!
-[screaming]
-There's a fire!
Stop them at the door!
[screaming and shouting]
[Double] Fire! There's a fire!
-Fuck you, asshole!
-Come with me!
-I'm an officer of the law!
-Stick it up your butthole, officer!
We're all free! Everybody!
-Bianca!
-Everybody's free!
-What's happening?
-Papa, what happened?
-Nothing. I scratched myself.
Come on. Through here.
-[Double] Everybody's free!
-[Diego] Come on.
Papa, I didn't know you sang.
That was so cool!
Okay, come on.
["Harlem River" by Kevin Morby playing]
[shouting and screaming]
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Whoo-oo ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Whoo-oo-oo ♪
♪ Harlem River, talk to me ♪
♪ Tell me what you think about ♪
♪ Harlem River,
I'm in love, love, love, love ♪
♪ Harlem River, talk to me ♪
♪ Where we heading now? ♪
♪ Harlem River,
I'm in love, love, love, love ♪
♪ All because of you ♪
♪ In my pearl and my diamond shoes ♪
♪ I've climbed the cloud
Now I store the moon ♪
♪ Harlem River ♪
♪ All because of you ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Whoo-oo… ♪
[Clara] Um…
So, the fine, how much was it?
Oh, so, you're interested?
-Nineteen thousand euros.
-My God!
For a song,
that seems a little excessive--
You falsified a permit.
And insulted the police.
You beat them up. You assaulted them.
[Clara sighs]
There was this kid, 17 years old,
doing heroin. Smoking it mostly.
But his passion was pills, chemistry.
And there were, well, snowballs, ecstasy.
LSD trips.
Lysergic acid gives a person
singular, fantastic visions.
It comes with a high toll.
Terrifying visions, a lot of horror.
One day, one of the few friends
he has left called him.
He visited his friend
and the little brother
of the friend
who had just bought a brand-new moped.
With a helmet. A new, beautiful helmet.
Bright colors, very expensive.
And he asked to borrow this helmet.
Of course, the kid says no
because he cares, it was new.
And somehow, through a kind of game,
he manages to tie the friend
and his brother up together.
As soon as they're pinned down,
he takes the helmet anyway
and their wallets.
Then he sells the helmet,
buys an impossible amount of drugs,
and takes them all
like there's no tomorrow.
He has answers to give the medics
who carry his stretcher to the ambulance,
but he finds he can't articulate
the words, can't seem to speak at all.
He feels scared.
Do you know what I knew in that moment?
That even though I was pissed off
at something or other,
and wanted to destroy the world,
the person I was screwing over was myself.
I realized that if I used
one ounce of that energy
to do something
other than being pissed off,
then, perhaps, I could do
something useful with my life.
In that moment, I decided and I did it.
The top 100 restaurants.
Do you realize what you've done here?
-[Clara chuckles]
-Huh? [chuckles]
It's incredible.
And you had them all working.
And they weren't ashamed. They were proud.
And then you destroyed everything.
I can't quite understand why.
You always want to be
the worst you can be.
[Clara sobs]
Here.
-What is it?
-A transfer to a facility for residents.
-[Clara] What do you mean?
-It's a state transfer.
What does "residential" mean?
I sleep there?
-Yes.
-No. No. I don't want to go there.
-Sorry.
-[voice breaking] No.
-You're done here. It's out of my hands.
-No.
[Clara sobs]
[sniffs]
-Is Diego coming too?
-No, he'll remain here.
He will be reprimanded, obviously,
but he'll stay with the course.
Do you know why I relate to you?
Because that young man
is always there.
I have to fight him every day.
Good luck, Clara.
[distant chatter]
[Clara] Excuse me.
Hello.
-Anna?
-Hmm.
I was awake.
Sure.
I'd fall asleep
if I was surrounded by all this too.
Huh.
Well, um…
I just stopped by
to wish you a Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Will I see you tomorrow?
Tomorrow? No.
Um…
I'm probably coming
a little bit less this month.
What is it? You're sad.
Really, you look like shit, though.
[chuckles]
Well…
it's not only my face that's shitty.
I'm just…
all wrong, I suppose.
I do things that make no sense,
no sense at all.
I tell lies all the time just because.
And I'm sick of my own bullshit.
That's all.
Perhaps you're right.
But to me, you are the best thing
that has ever happened.
[Adelaide breathes deeply]
I'll see you tomorrow
for some meatballs with red sauce, okay?
The owner wants you
to keep doing the one meal per day thing.
We like the idea of exclusivity.
Oh… Uh…
Oh…
If you follow me,
I'll show you the kitchen.
Hmm…
Uh, how did the interview go?
How did it go?
Good, I think.
What does it pay?
Uh… tortellini?
Did you make them?
[Diego's dad chuckles]
Five thousand euros a month, they said.
Excuse me, but you say 5,000 a month,
and make that face, huh?
Know what I should've done
when you were a kid?
I should've kicked you in the legs
until they were red
like your face right now!
Sure, how about two big kicks for a boy
who doesn't even have a mother, right?
And maybe add a couple of hits
while we're at it, why don't you?
Look, Diego.
All right, draw a line.
Focus on what you do have.
Don't think anymore
about those who didn't want you.
Because in the meantime,
some of us wanted you very much.
Those of us who wanted you so, so much…
[bangs table]
…that they put up with your entire
adolescence,
which, trust me,
it was Vietnam.
Uh…
And this person,
this someone, who is me,
he loved you unconditionally…
for the person you are,
which is an enormous, immense
pain in the ass.
All right, you're a little unhinged,
but we've made it this far, right?
And that's not for everyone.
Trust me.
I just don't feel like taking
this job by myself, you know?
[sighs] All right, then draw another line.
This young lady,
who, yes, has her own faults,
but she supports you.
So, look,
keep her close to you.
Keep her close.
Hmm.
[soft piano music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] The shared bathroom
is near the stairs.
Dinner's from 8:00 to 9:00.
In the morning at 6:00,
the bus comes to take you to the archives,
then brings you back at 3:00.
This is your room, and this is your bed.
They want you downstairs
in an hour for group.
And welcome.
Thank you.
A journey to the center
of the Earth and, uh…
with shoes in the sun, um, with everyone…
Now I'd like to read a lot faster.
[Chip continues indistinctly]
Good, but a bit temperamental,
because they jump from lane to lane,
doing cartwheels…
Come on in.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Sit down there.
They're really lively, and unfortunately,
my daughter brought them to me.
So, what can I do? Throw them in the pool?
I can't throw them in the pool. I can't.
Ah, yes, very much.
[Diego] Hmm…
Hmm…
You… disappeared.
Uh… Uh…
So what?
[Diego] Uh…
Hey!
You can't just disappear
from one moment to the next, huh?
Who let you in here? What do you want?
Huh? You said
I'm not good enough for you, right?
What do you need?
A nurse? What do you want?
[Diego] Listen, listen. Hey!
Listen, listen, listen.
I… was missing a piece.
Okay? I've always been missing
a piece, okay?
Now I've… found it.
You know it and I know it. Hmm…
And I feel happy because I'm pretty sure
that… that… that I'm able to live better,
so you… you can't disappear, okay?
You said it.
You said I was a problem.
You said that we were two problems,
we're two fucking problems.
You know what two problems together are?
-A big mess.
-No.
-A fucking big mess--
-No, no, no, they make two…
They make two
who understand each other,
which nobody…
nobody… nobody gets but us.
And so it doesn't matter
that I'm a person with a stutter.
It doesn't… it doesn't matter anymore,
because to you,
it's all the same thing.
Of course I don't mind.
And you too,
I don't understand all the crap you say,
but it doesn't matter at all
because to me, you're fine.
Because you're fine,
because that's exactly the person you are.
And you're fine, really,
just how you are.
Hmm…
We're still two problems.
No, no, we're like, um…
Like pizza with figs.
Uh, like, like, like, uh…
balsamic with chocolate,
which seems like you'd say,
"That doesn't make sense,"
instead, but you don't understand how…
Hmm…
Uh…
Oh…
We have to take this
from the top, all right?
Okay, but I want to be the chocolate.
Uh…
Hmm…
And, please,
throw out the gum for me.
-[Clara] Oh…
-[Diego] Hmm…
[Clara sobs]
Uh, if that's how you react, I'll…
[Diego chuckles]
[Clara chuckles]
[Clara sighs deeply]
Hmm…
You don't really think
I have a big ass, do you?
Well, yes.
Yes, but I… I like it,
because you're… you're really soft.
-[Clara chuckling]
-Yes.
Yes.
What… what was it
you called me that one time?
-[Clara] When?
-[Diego] Something about a peanut?
-[Clara] When did I say that?
-[Diego] A bunch of times.
[Clara laughs] Are you sure I said that?
["Nei tuoi occhi"
by Francesca Michielin playing]
[ambient music playing]